(Howard:)So dinner went nice.
(Bernadette:)Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
(Bernadette:)Does your mother always cut your meat
for you?
(Howard:)Only when it's fatty.
(Howard:)Well, don't be jealous, babe.
(Howard:)Someday, you'll get to cut it for me.
(Sheldon:)Bernadette,
I found the extra head for the Water Pik...
...if you wanna use it.
(Bernadette:)I'm okay, Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I just squirted
haIf a brisket out of my teeth.
(Howard:)Hey, Ma, how about a little privacy?
Oh, I know what that means. Hubba-hubba.
- Oh, God.
- Relax, it'll be fine.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
Heh.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Let me know when you're done canoodling.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Mommy needs a foot rub.
Do a little dance
Make a little love